安东尼奥
Hey, Antonio.
抱歉
Sorry.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah, yeah.
-我没事  没事  -好吧
- I'm good, I'm good. - Good.
-你没事吧  -没事  很好
- You good? - Good, yeah, all good.
-嗯  -你要进去吗
- Yeah. - Are you going in?
好  我也是
Good, me too.
-走吗  -好的
- Should we walk? - Yeah.
好的
Okay.
我很高兴我们俩能这样共处
Well I for one am very glad that we can be together
一点都不尴尬
and it's not awkward.
你是为普拉特的事来的吗
Are you here for Platt's thing?
因为我这辈子还没见穆奇
'Cause I've never seen Mouch so excited
这么激动过
about anything in his whole life.
他为此还专门做了一个
He made a cinnamon roll casserole
肉桂卷砂锅
for the occasion.
那是什么东西
What the hell's that?
有什么大不了的  伙计  帮我个忙
What's the big deal, man? Just do me this favor.
我不会在推特上直播几句话
I'm not live tweeting a three-minute conversation.
那才几句话
It's a three-minute conversation.
本地人都能去  穆奇  我是说...
Local access, Mouch, I mean--
你准备让谁来发布
Who do you propose is going to be tuning in
这些推特
for these live tweets?
你来这里干什么
What are you doing here?
警署不是在召开自己的观映派对吗
I thought PD was having their own viewing party.
三十分钟后就开始了
She's on in 30 minutes.
虽然我爱特鲁迪  我还是为伊娃来的
As much as I love Trudy. I'm here for Eva.
-你们看到她了吗  -她和加比一起
- You guys seen her? - She's down there with Gabby.
三楼左手边的房间
Third door on the left.
特鲁迪·普拉特直播
电视首秀
好了  长发公主
There you go, Rapunzel.
收拾好东西我们走
Get your stuff. We're going.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
你说我今天都可以和加比阿姨一起的
You said I could hang with Aunt Gabby all day.
是啊  她没事的
Yeah, she can. She's fine.
不行  你被禁足了
You're not staying. You're grounded.
不许打电话  不许上社交媒体
No more phone. No social media.
-走吧  -什么  我做了什么
- Let's go. - What? What did I do?
好吧  这不是你看上去那样
All right, that's not what it looks like.
-我能解释  -这是你的资料吗
- I can explain. - Is that not your profile?
-没错  但不是...  -用的假名
- No, it is, but it's not-- - Under a fake name
-这样我就监控不到了  -不
- so I can't monitor it. - No.
这只是一个小号
It's just a second account.
这是我和我朋友用的
It's the one I use at my friends--
这是一个你发布自己
It's the account where you posted a dozen pictures
派对喝酒照片的账号
of yourself partying and drinking.
我没有发布那些照片
I did not post any of those.
-上周末...  -那是
- Last weekend--Hey! - That was--
上周末你告诉我
Last weekend when you told me
你在塔琳家学习到很晚
you were studying late at Taryn's house.
-你不是这么和我说的吗  -我...
- Did you not tell me that? - I--
去收拾东西
Go get your stuff.
别看她  快去
Don't look at her. Go.
伊娃  把你的手机给我
Eva, give me your phone.
你知道你看上去和爸爸一模一样吧
You know you look just like Dad, right?
连前额上都会和他一样爆出青筋
You even got that forehead vein thing going.
爸爸就是这样
That's papa.
走吧
Come on. Let's go.
回见  伊娃
Later, Eva.
我认识的每个人都有两个账号
Every single person I know has two profiles.
只是为了私人空间
It's just for privacy.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
那不叫私人空间  那叫隐瞒
That's not privacy. That's hiding.
你把这些照片的意思都曲解了
You're making those photos into something they're not.
你不能相信网络  爸爸
You can't trust the Internet, Dad.
那看上去总是更严重一些
It always looks worse than it is.
翻译     小酸奶   Lynn_宁   H小欠
如果你能让我和你解释一下
If you would just let me explain it to you
而不是无缘无故没收我的手机
instead of you seizing my phone without cause.
翻译     小萝莉   不高兴童鞋   圈圈
普拉特两分钟后出场  大家准备  亚当
Platt's on in two. Everyone! Adam!
-安东尼奥  快来  -我们要走了
- Antonio, come on. - We're not staying.
我回家处理文件
I'm gonna do the paperwork at home.
校对     圈圈
伊娃  怎么样  孩子
Hey, Eva. What's up, kid?
我爸爸是个法西斯
My father's a fascist.
好吧  我也不知道怎么办
Okay, I don't know what to do with that.
时间轴     chance-coco   西查
大家都安静
Okay, everybody be quiet.
普拉特在电视上
Platt's on TV.
警察近距离接触
贝蒂要和这位来自芝加哥警局
Betty's sitting down to discuss
后期     8T
和善的特鲁迪·普拉特警长
the new friendly face of the Chicago PD
进行深入的交流
with Sergeant Trudy Platt.
-这算什么和善  -说的是贝蒂
- What friendly face is that? - Betty.
总监     圈圈
谢谢你  雪莉
Thank you, Sheri.
警察近距离接触
新项目进展顺利
很高兴今天能在这里
I'm so excited to be here today
贝蒂·霍德  特鲁迪·普拉特警长
和21分局的特鲁迪·普拉特警长一起...
with Sergeant Trudy Platt from the 21st District...
她不能更讨厌这一套了
She couldn't possibly hate this any more.
谢谢你的到来
Thank you so much for coming this morning.
警察近距离接触
新项目进展顺利
我很荣幸  我很高...高兴能来到这里
It's my pleasure. I'm hap--I'm happy to be here.
这简直就像是过圣诞
Oh, this is like Christmas.
这些照片表现得并不是你看上去那样
Those photos don't show what you think they do.
我们的确去了塔琳家  然后我们接到
Okay, we did go to Taryn's house, and then we got a call
-贝卡的电话说她需要...  -伊娃  别说了
- from Becca that she needed-- - Eva, stop!
你的人生都发在上面了
You put your whole life on that thing.
我不需要你解释
I don't need you to explain.
我可以看到你在做什么
I can see exactly what you're doing
你是谁  你知道吗
and who you are. And you know what?
我不喜欢你现在变成的样子
I don't like who you've become very much.
在我们服务的区域
In the neighborhoods that they serve.
警察近距离接触
新项目进展顺利
与犯罪作斗争
Combating crime problems together
和...
along with--
-没事吧  -我觉得这声音
- Is everything okay? - I think that's coming
-是从我办公室传出来的  -什么声音
- from my office. - What was that?
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第十六集
警官
Hey, Officer.
我是汉克·博伊特警长
Sergeant Hank Voight.
现在还没有设指挥台吗
There's no command post set yet?
-没有  长官  还没有  -好的
- No, sir. Not yet. - Okay.
-你叫什么  -乔伊
- What's your name? - Joey.
-门德斯  门德斯警官  -听着
- Mendez. Officer Mendez. - Okay, listen.
你知道怎么设警戒线吗  门德斯
You know how to set up cordon, Mendez?
很好
All right, good.
我要你在三个街区外
I want you to establish it
设立警戒线
around a three-block radius.
任何人不得进出
No one in or out
除了救护者和伤者
except first responders and victims.
你要设立一个等候区
All right, you set up a holding area.
-让一下  -收集所有人的资料
- Excuse me. - Get everyone's info.
搞清楚身份前谁都不许走
No one leaves if you don't know 'em.
明白了吗  去吧
You got it? Go.
特鲁迪
Trudy!
-特鲁迪  -警长
- Trudy! - Sarge!
爆炸发生七分钟了
Seven minutes since the explosion.
火灾没有燃气痕迹
Fire has no reads on gas meters.
也还没有普拉特的消息
And we haven't heard from Platt yet.
贝蒂  贝蒂
Betty? Betty?
贝蒂
Betty.
雪莉
Sheri?
雪莉  雪莉
Sheri? Sheri?
没事的
Hey, it's going to be okay.
雪莉  雪莉
Sheri. Sheri.
雪莉  坚持住
Sheri, stay with me. Come on.
没事的  雪莉
It's okay, Sheri.
出口被堵住了
The exits are blocked.
我们不能上楼
We can't get upstairs.
我们进这里
We'll go in here.
过来
Come on.
雪莉  你还能坚持住吗
Sheri, are you still with me?
雪莉
Sheri.
加油  姑娘  坚持住
Come on, girl. Stay with me.
坚持住  雪莉
Stay with me, Sheri.
加油  姑娘
Come on, girl.
好了  姑娘
Okay, girl.
呼吸  呼吸
Breathe. Breathe.
穆奇
呼叫失败
-呼吸  亲爱的  -消防局  大声呼救
- Breathe, honey. - Fire department. Call out!
这边
Here!
Here.
特鲁迪  特鲁迪  你没事吧
Trudy? Trudy. You okay?
-我没事  救她  -你没事吧
- I'm okay. Get her. - You okay?
我没事  救她
I'm okay. Get her.
-我来  我来  -好的
- I got her, I got her. - Okay.
-你没事吧  -嗯  我没事
- You're okay? - Yeah, yeah, I'm okay.
-克鲁兹就在我后面  -好的
- Cruz is right behind me. - Okay.
他在前门那里搜救
He's covering the front entrance.
好
Okay.
坚持住  雪莉  好
Stay with us, Sheri. Okay.
-你可以走吗  -可以
- Hey, you good to go? - Yeah, I'm good to go.
-你确定  -确定
- You sure? - Good to go.
好  跟着我  压低重心
All right, just follow me, stay low.
我带你去找克鲁兹
I'm gonna get you back to Cruz.
他会带你上楼的  知道了吗
He's gonna take you upstairs, okay?
-嗯  -好  我们走
- Yeah. - All right, let's move.
坚持住  雪莉  我们走
Stay with us, Sheri. Here we go.
医生
Medic!
我需要医生
I need a medic!
特鲁迪
Trudy!
我没事
I'm okay.
雪莉的伤是由螺栓和钉子造成的
Sheri's wounds are from bolts and nails.
这是一起爆炸案  先是计时器响
This was a bombing. First the timer sounded.
紧接着不到三十秒  就发生了爆炸
Less than 30 seconds later, the explosion.
好  做好准备  让1800赶来现场
All right, get on the zone. Get 1800 on the scene.
让爆炸纵火处理人员来清查是否还有其他装置
We need Bomb and Arson sweeping for secondary devices.
收到
Copy that.
-你确定你没事  -快去
- You sure you're okay? - Go, go, go, go, go.
-她还有脉搏  -好  我们来处理
- She had a pulse. - Okay, we got it.
脉象平稳  应该没事
It was steady. She should be okay.
普拉特  普拉特  普拉特  我们来就行
Platt. Platt, Platt! We got it.
-没事的  -雪莉  你会没事的
- It's fine. - Sheri, you're gonna be okay.
特鲁迪
Trudy!
-到底怎么回事  -我没事我没事
- What the hell happened? - I'm okay. I'm okay.
-我真的没事  -快来  快来
- I am. I'm okay. - Come on, come on.
-医护人员  给我条毯子  -好
- Medic! Give me a blanket. - Yep.
不  女士
No, ma'am.
不要说话  我们会帮助你的
Don't try and speak. We got you.
-我们这就送你去医院  -必须要跟...
- We're going to the hospital. - Must talk to...
不要说话
Don't try and speak.
我不走
I won't go.
-必须要跟警察说  -好了女士
- Must talk to cop. - Okay, ma'am, all right.
-我们会给你找警察来的  -不
- We're gonna get you a cop. - No.
-不  -安东尼奥
- No. - Antonio.
-我要警察  -她不让我们走
- Need a cop! - She won't let us leave
除非先跟警察说话  我们没有时间了
until she talks to a cop. We don't have time.
-必须赶紧出发  -我跟你们走
- We got to move. - I'll come.
不
No.
快快快
Let's go. Let's go.
女士  你要明白继续说话
Ma'am, you understand that by continuing to speak
会对你造成生命危险
you're putting yourself at risk?
我不建议你说话
I don't recommend it.
-说  -我在这里
- Talk. - I'm here.
我在这里我在这里
I'm here. I'm here.
我是安东尼奥·道森
I'm Antonio Dawson.
是芝加哥警署的一名警探
I'm a detective with the Chicago Police Department.
听着  你不必现在说话
Listen, we don't have to talk right now.
我想...
I want...
我想...我想说
I wanna--I want to talk.
好好好
Okay, okay. Okay.
有...
There...
有一个包...包裹
was a pa--package...
-给我的  -包裹
- for me. - A package?
我觉得应该是...那个炸弹
I think it was... the--the bomb.
你认为包裹里面装有炸弹
You think there was a bomb in the package?
是给你的
For you?
它寄到了我的...我的办公室
It was delivered to my--my office.
好好好
Okay, okay, okay.
我被人恐吓了
I've been threatened.
你知道是谁寄的吗
Do you know who sent it?
安东尼奥  她的心率加快了
Antonio, her heart rate's going up.
不知道  但是有个男人
No, but there was a man
我见...见过
who I...I've already seen.
-好  -四十多岁
- Okay. - 40s.
有胡子  他...
Beard. He...
让开
Move.
我能做点什么  能帮上什么忙
What can I do? How can I help?
向她的颈部施压
Put pressure on her neck.
流了好多血
There's a lot of blood coming up.
雪莉  能听见我说话吗
Hey. Hey, Sheri, you hear me?
雪莉  保持清醒  雪莉
Sheri? Stay with me, Sheri!
好了  我们拿到了爆炸纵火人员的初步调查
All right, we got the initial report from Bomb and Arson.
只有一个装置
It was a single device.
就在雪莉办公室里的纸盒里
Cardboard box in Sheri's office.
简易爆炸装置  钉子  玻璃
IED, nails, glass.
还好当时没人离炸弹更近  警长
We're lucky no one was standing closer, Sarge.
雪莉已经在医院宣告死亡了
Sheri was pronounced at Med.
她...
She, uh--
伤势太过严重
Injuries were too substantial.
其他两人情况也很危急
Two others are in critical condition,
但医生预计他们都能度过危险期
but they're both suspected to pull through.
还有十多名伤者  但目前看来
There was a dozen more victims but as of right now
只有雪莉和贝蒂不幸丧生
it looks like Sheri and Betty are our only fatalities.
炸弹被放置在了雪莉的办公室
That bomb was planted in Sheri's office.
目标一定就是她
She had to be the target.
她也收到了恐吓信
She was getting threats too.
我们复原了四封邮件
We recovered four emails all sent
都是从一个匿名账号发来的
from an anonymous email account.
大约转了六个IP地址
Bounced around about a half dozen IPs.
全都是死亡恐吓
They're all death threats.
"烧死吧贱人  死去吧  你没剩几天了
"Burn, bitch, burn. Your days are numbered.
"你马上就会死了"之类的
You will burn." That sort of thing.
好  我们对雪莉了解多少
All right, so what do we know about Sheri?
她今年26岁  西北大学毕业
She's 26 years old, Northwestern grad,
以实习生身份开始在这家电视台工作
started working for the station as an intern.
她已经做了两个月的节目了
She'd been on the air for two months.
单身  人缘很好  埃尔现在和她的家人在一起
Single, well-liked. Al's with the family.
我们正试图追踪这件包裹
Trying to track the package.
大楼入口处的摄像头只拍到了
Cameras at the entrances of the building
一名男子的背影
only captured a man from behind.
不算很有用  但根据这个以及雪莉给出的信息
It's not much, but given that and what Sheri gave us
我调出了这些照片
I pulled these pod photos.
可能会是同一个人
Could be the same guy
如果他丢掉了外套和帽子
if he ditches the jacket and the hat.
这个人是在早上8:42离开的新闻编辑室
This guy exits the newsroom at 8:42 a.m.
半小时后一个摄像头拍到他在马路对面
Half hour later a pod picks him up across the street.
这是爆炸发生后八分钟  他还在那里
It's eight minutes after the bombing and he's still there.
就好像他是一直待在那里的
Like, he stayed.
他符合雪莉的描述
He matches Sheri's description.
嗯  可这不够我们进行相貌识别
Yeah, but it's not enough for visual recognition.
那我们就把它泄露给媒体
Okay, let's release it to the media.
说他是嫌疑犯  开通举报专线
It's a person of interest. Set up a tip line.
确定这个计划可行吗
Are we sure that's the plan?
我们只是拿到了附近一个男人的两张照片
We got two pictures of a guy in the vicinity.
仅此而已
That's it.
如果让公众拿到这些照片
That can go wrong a thousand ways
事态可能会超出控制
if the public has it.
我身上还沾着雪莉的血
I still have Sheri's blood on me.
要是问我的话  我认为这个险值得冒
You asking me, it's worth the risk.
总会有人知道这个人是谁
Someone's gonna know who this guy is.
我这就联系新闻部门
I'll get on the packs with news affairs.
发布这些照片
Have them release it.
查到线索了
We got something.
我问了新闻编辑室
I interviewed the guard who was working
前台的保安
the front desk at the news room.
他说所有人必须签字后才能进入
He says everyone has to sign in to get inside.
他记得今天早上只来了一个快递
He only remembers one delivery from this morning
那人进来的时候他正好在打电话
and he was on the phone when the guy came in.
但他发誓那个人是白人  还有胡子
But he swears he was white and he had a beard.
所以这个人在寄送炸弹之前
This guy's stopped by security
被保安拦下来过
before he delivered the bomb?
这个人...
This guy...
在出入登记簿上签下了名字
signed his name in the in-out book.
埃里克·米切尔  是一家
Eric Mitchel, he's a journalist
当地娱乐杂志社的记者
at a local entertainment magazine.
35岁  白人  络腮胡
35, white, beard.
带他来局里
Bring him in.
-这记者住得可真不错  -是啊
- Nice house for a journalist. - Yeah.
我还以为新闻业已经彻底完蛋了呢
I thought journalism was supposed to be extinct.
得看是哪种新闻了
Depends what kind.
把新闻变成娱乐的人
Still have a lot of money
还是能挣很多钱的
if you make the news entertainment.
那个人是米切尔吗
Hey, is that Mitchel?
对  车牌号是他的
Yeah, those are his plates.
开SUV的人是米切尔
SUV is Mitchel.
我们打算步行接近  分散他注意力
So we're gonna approach on foot, distract him.
你们从背后阻截他
You guys come up behind him.
收到  这就行动
Copy. We're moving in now.
看来他把胡子给剃了啊
Looks like he shaved his beard.
-埃里克·米切尔  -什么事
- Eric Mitchel. - Yeah?
-你还好吗  -我没事
- You okay? - Yeah, I'm good.
快上报
All right, call it in.
5021H  紧急情况
5021 Henry. Emergency.
-发生爆炸...  -你们没事吧
- We have an explosion at... - You guys good?
-没事  你呢  -我们得给他遮一下
- Yeah, you? - We got to get him covered up.
救护车  消防局  爆炸纵火调查局
Ambulance, CFD, Bomb and Arson.
可能会有多爆炸装置
Could be multiple devices.
确保警戒线半径有2个街区
Make sure they block off a two-block radius.
整个爆炸迎面炸向他  他已经死了
The entire blast hit him head on. He's gone.
我看到事故发生了  我能做什么
Hey. I saw it happen. What can I do?
-我就在那儿  -先生  请你退后
- I was right over there. - Sir, I need you to step back.
-要我帮忙吗  -是  我知道你想帮忙
- Can I help? - Yeah, I know you want to help
-但请退后  -我能做什么
- but I need you to stand back. - What can I do?
谢谢配合
Thank you.
拆弹组和纵火调查组证实了
Okay, Bomb and Arson confirmed
炸弹是接在信箱门上的
the bomb was wired to the mailbox door.
可能有人目击到炸弹安装
It's possible someone saw the bomb being planted.
中心警局和巡逻队在挨家挨户走访
Area Central and Patrol are canvassing the neighborhood.
我们在查监控上的录像
We're running pods against surveillance
但目前为止毫无进展
but so far we've got nothing.
我们知道埃里克·米切尔不是设炸弹的人
We know Eric Mitchel's not our bomber
我们刚看到他被炸飞了
being we just watched him get blown up.
这算什么
What the hell are we looking at?
那个混蛋引我们过去的
This son of a bitch led us there.
他在耍我们
He's screwing with us.
他用下一个目标的名字签字
He signed in using the name of
把我们引上钩
his next target so we'd follow.
没错  这不是一次独立的事件
That's right. This is not an isolated incident.
好吗  这可能是一系列炸弹活动的开始
Okay? This could be the start of a bombing campaign.
这个人有自己的计划
This guy's got an agenda.
关于埃里克·米切尔我们知道多少
All right, what do we know about Eric Mitchel.
他在媒体业工作15年
Well, he worked in media 15 years.
在娱乐杂志做记者
Journalist at an entertainment magazine.
没有对他死亡威胁的证据
There's no evidence of death threats against him,
但不代表没有电话或
but that doesn't mean that it didn't happen
面对面的威胁
over the phone or face-to-face.
拆弹组  纵火调查组和重案组
Bomb and Arson and Homicide
在我们说话这会正在挖出更多消息
are digging up more as we speak.
说真的  如果再有人问我是不是还好
Seriously, if one more person asks me if I'm okay
他们可不会好过
they are not gonna be okay.
我只是想帮忙
I just want to help.
好的
And we'll take it.
拆弹组和纵火调查组有进展了
Bomb and Arson's got an update.
我也过去
I'll come with.
我们用现有信息
Okay, so we're gonna go
-继续跟进调查  -我没事
- with what we got, okay? - I'm okay.
-好  -炸弹信息
- Okay. - The bombs themselves,
两个受害者的身份信息
the IDs of these two victims.
我们知道他们都在媒体工作
We know they're both in the media.
他们之间会有关联
There's some connection between these two.
他们被选为目标是有原因的
There's a reason they were targeted.
在下一起爆炸案发生前我们要找到关联
So let's find the damn nexus before another bomb goes off.
来  特鲁迪  我告诉你进展
Come on, Trudy. I'll give you an update.
我说明白了
I'm talking clean.
这不是什么顽皮小子用父亲的
This isn't some teenage wank screwing around
家得宝账户捣蛋
with his dad's Home Depot account.
电线  引发器  线路板
The wires, the initiators, the circuit board,
这些东西上面的连接物
the soldering alone on these things.
是一个明白自己在做什么的人干的
It's by someone who knew what they were doing.
是花了时间去做的
Took their time to do it.
根据他安置炸弹的爆炸位置
Devices were personalized
装置都是有个人特征的
based on the location he was hitting.
第一个装置是基于时间开关器的自制炸弹
The first device was an IED relying on a time switch.
设计为在封闭空间内
It was created to invoke as much damage as possible
引起尽可能大的破坏
within an enclosed space.
滚珠  钉子  螺栓
The ball bearings, the nails, the bolts.
加上足够的汽油蔓延大火
Plus enough gasoline to spread hefty fire.
那么和第二起不同吗
All right, so that's different from our second?
第二起是受害者激活的自制炸弹
The second is a victim-activated IED.
米切尔打开信箱就会引发爆炸
It was triggered when Mitchel opened up his mailbox.
所以两个不同的模式  但你说是一个人所为
So two different models but you're saying this is one guy?
对  是完全一样的原料
Yeah, it's the exact same materials,
一样的特征  就和手写笔迹一样
same signature. It's like handwriting.
一个人设计出这两样东西
Same brain built both of these things.
好  那这些螺栓  钉子  电线
Okay, so these bolts, the nails, the wires
甚至汽油  我都可以在
the gasoline even, I can purchase
五金店买到  对吧
that stuff at a hardware store, right?
可以  但你买不到C4炸药
You could but you couldn't buy the C-4.
两个炸弹都用的军用级别的C4
Both bombs used military-grade C-4.
你在街边买不到那种
All right, you can't buy that kind of C-4
C4炸药  而军方有详尽的
over the counter, and the military keeps strict records
-失窃和保存记录  -在黑市上
- on theft and storage. - It had to be either stolen
肯定有偷窃或买卖信息
or bought on the black market.
我在烟酒枪支管理局顺着这个方向查
I'm digging at an angle with ATF.
剩下的炸弹零件
Yeah, rest of the bomb components
就很难查了  都是随处可见的
are gonna be hard to track. They're generic.
-到处都能买到  -好
- Sold in hundreds of stores. - All right.
他们之间的关联查得怎么样
Where are we at with the connection?
没有  埃里克和雪莉没有工作交集
Nowhere. Eric and Sheri never worked together.
没有做过同一则报道
They never reported on the same story.
都没有证据表明他们互相认识
There's no evidence they really even knew each other.
安东尼奥  你的热线电话有消息了
Antonio, your tip line sparked something,
但我们要快点行动
but we got to move fast.
有人打进来  指认了探头里的照片
Somebody called in, identified the pod photos.
马克·特莱蒙  身高  体重
Mark Tremon. Height, weight.
和技术部告诉我们的相符
Match everything the tech lab already told us about.
他在新闻站点做安保两年了
He worked security at the news station for two years
而且他去伊利诺斯州的时间
and he went to Illinois State
和埃里克·米切尔一样
the same time Eric Mitchel did.
这就是两个受害者间的关联
That's the nexus between our victims,
但还不是最惊人的部分
but that's not even the crazy part.
他是军人  警长
He's army, Sarge.
在伊拉克服役过  EOD
Did a tour in Iraq. EOD.
拆弹处理小组
Explosive Ordinance Disposal.
你俩去调查他吗
All right, you two round robin?
伯吉斯和鲁塞克已经在去他家的路上了
Burgess and Ruzek are already headed to his house,
但我们要快点
but we need to move
因为网络上都炸了
because the Internet is blowing him up.
他们已经认出照片了
They already ID'd the photos.
他会知道我们来的
He gonna see us coming.
我去那边和他们碰头
I'll meet them there.
干得好
Nice work.
我们的电话响个没完
Our phone's been ringing off the hook.
我们要带你丈夫走
We just need to bring your husband in
-问几个问题  -怎么回事
- to ask a few questions. - What is all that?
女士  你丈夫  你知道他在哪儿吗
Ma'am, your husband. Do you know where he is?
你们不可以进我家
We're not giving you consent to enter our home.
先生  您可以出来吗
Sir, can you step outside, please?
不  我哪里也不去
No, I'm not stepping anywhere.
怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
举起手来
I want to see both of your hands!
开玩笑吧
You got to be kidding me.
别拦住我女儿
Get away from my daughter!
过来  姑娘
Just come through, baby.
她可以过来
She can come through.
别碰我女儿
Don't put your hands on my daughter.
-让她  -别碰她
- Let her -Hey, man!
别碰我女儿
Hey! Hey! Don't touch my daughter!
-爸爸  -别碰我女儿
- Dad, dad! - Hey, don't touch my daughter.
别碰我女儿
Don't touch my daughter!
-不  -放开我
- No! - Get off of me!
-冷静  -放开我
- Calm down! - Get off me!
-没事的  -没事的
- It's all right, baby. - You're fine.
没事的  女儿
It's all right, baby.
-抓住他的手了吗  -放开我
- You got his hands? - Get off me.
我不想他在这里
I don't want him here.
好
Okay.
但我告诉你  现在你在这房间里
I got to tell you though, this room you're in?
不是你想怎样就怎样
It's not a place you get a lot of things you want.
你知道自己为什么在这里吧
I mean, you know why you're here, right?
我已经被审过两次了
I've already been interviewed twice.
你们的两个警探
Two of your detectives.
现在你得跟我说
Well you're gonna talk to me now.
我在这里是因为你
I'm here because of you.
警方把我的照片通过推特发出去
Police tweet out a picture of me.
把我按在地上  按在这椅子上
Push me to the ground, put me in this chair--
你在这里是因为他们
You're here 'cause of them.
一天内的3位爆炸受害者
Three bombing victims, one day.
我告诉过你们警官  我当时在新闻站点
I told your officers, I was at that news station
让别人填写推荐信表格
to get someone to fill out a form of reference.
问题是
Yeah, well the problem is
我们没发现相关证据
we can't find any evidence of that.
你没有表格  也没人记得
You don't have the form, and no one remembers.
我把它扔了
I threw it out!
我走进去  以前的老板不在
I walked in there. Old boss wasn't there.
我就出去了
So I walked out.
网上说我是恶人
The Internet tells you I'm some villain
你们就信了
and you believe it?
我是个普通人
I'm a regular guy.
你不是普通人
You're not a regular guy.
警戒线围住的时候
You're a guy who was at the scene
你在爆炸现场
of an explosion that was cordoned off.
你知道警戒线吗
Do you know what a police cordon is?
所有目击者和市民都在包围内
All witnesses and civilians go into holding,
而你不在  说明你绕过了
and you weren't in holding, which means you bypassed
警戒线
the police department cordon.
我得回家照顾孩子
I had to get back home to my kid.
你认识雪莉
You're a guy who knew Sheri,
也认识埃里克
knew Eric.
-埃里克是谁  -他是你爱荷华州立大学的同学
- Who the hell is Eric? - He went to ISU with you.
什么  我就上了一个月的学
What? I went to school for like a month.
这是你跟两名受害者的关联
That's access to both our victims.
-满嘴放屁...  -你以前是拆弹小组的
- This is bull-- - And you were EOD.
你说什么
Excuse me?
你了解简易爆炸装置
You know IEDs!
是吗
Right?
你就是拆他们的
You defused them.
我打赌你也会造
I'll bet you can make them.
-我要律师  -你说得越多
- Give me a lawyer. - The more you talk to us
-越容易...  -我要律师
- the easier it is-- - Get a damn lawyer.
告诉我有进展了
All right, tell me we got something
因为马克什么都没说
'cause Mark ain't talking
我们没有足够的证据起诉他
and we don't have enough to charge.
马克和受害者之间
Well, the nexus between Mark
的确有联系
and the victims is real,
但是还不够紧到
but it's just not tight enough
把他和埃里克联系起来
to connect him to Eric.
除了爱荷华州立大学
Outside of ISU,
他们之间并没有联系
there's no real link.
好了  C4呢
All right, what about the C-4?
烟酒枪支管理局的报告说这批特殊的C4
ATF's report says this particular batch of C-4
是6年前制造的
was made six years ago.
2012年很多地区的制造商
Multiple blocks were reported stolen
上报被偷
from the manufacturer in 2012.
2012年
Oh, 2012?
所以我们现在落后这个线索6年
So we're six years behind the lead.
不  我在烟酒枪支管理局有人
No, I got a guy in ATF.
我打听一下帮咱们赶上进度
I'll catch us up.
我们有什么可以用到这家伙身上的筹码吗
Do we have anything I can use as leverage on this guy?
马克去年酒驾
Mark's got a DUI from last year.
他骂了逮捕他的警官
He chewed out the arresting officer.
他是个易怒的人
He's an angry guy.
但是很多人都易怒
But a lot of people are angry,
特别是喝了几杯之后
especially after a few beers.
并不意味着他们会制造炸弹
Doesn't mean they build bombs.
如果我们什么都找不到的话
Look, if we're not finding anything
也许我们查错方向了
then maybe we're looking in the wrong place.
这家伙家里没有任何制作炸弹的材料
This guy's house was cleared of any bomb-making materials.
而且新闻台的保安
And the security guard at the news station
对他并没有印象
said he couldn't pick him out of a line up.
说句公道话  新闻台的保安怀疑
To be fair, the guard at the station
自己根本认不出那家伙
doubted he could ID the guy at all.
他说他没有看清楚
He said he didn't get a good look.
马克无法解释
And Mark has no explanation
他为什么在爆炸现场外站了八分钟
why he stood outside the bombing for eight minutes.
马克获得过卓越服役十字勋章
Mark's got a distinguished service cross.
那并不意味着什么
You know that doesn't mean anything.
那意味着他为国而战
It means he fought for the country and it means
意味着我目前假定他是无罪的  好吗
I give him the benefit of the doubt, all right?
也许我们的调查方向错了
Maybe we're looking in the wrong place.
我觉得这些联系很勉强
I think these connections seem pretty strained.
-杰  听着  -好了
- Jay, look-- - All right.
要么定罪要么无罪释放
Then cement or clear them.
给马克做个心理解剖
Do a psychological autopsy on Mark.
在过去的一周和他说过话的人
Anyone he's talked to in the last week.
任何可以解释他的行为的人
Anyone who can speak to his behavior.
收到
Copy that.
如果马克就是我们要找的人  肯定有人知道
If Mark is our man, someone's gonna know it.
那是什么
What's all that?
在社交媒体上追踪马克
Tracking Mark on social media.
很多人跳出来说
A lot of people coming out the woodwork saying
他们早知道会这样
they saw it coming,
所以我在核实有没有人说的是真话
and so I'm trying to verify if any of it's true.
-结果呢  -目前为止  没有进展
- And? - So far, nothing.
都是些见风使舵的键盘侠
Trolls jumping on the bandwagon.
真是难以相信他可能会逍遥法外
这家伙向来都是个烂人
人们喜欢火上浇油
People love to watch things burn.
马克
你怎么可以这么做
我希望你在地狱里腐烂
逮捕这个垃圾
干倒这傻逼
是什么让你伤害这些人的
是  马克的通话记录显示我们是朋友
Yeah, Mark's phone records indicate that we're friends
因为我们的确是朋友
'cause we are.
你们一起在WNMZ工作过  是吗
You worked at WNMZ together, yeah?
我在那待了一个月  并没有留下
I was there for a month. Didn't work out.
我没什么能帮到你们的
Look, guys, I can't do anything to help you.
我还要工作
And I'm at my job.
我们已经晚交货一个小时了
We're an hour late getting this shipment out.
好吧  我们只有几个问题  很快就好
Okay, well, we just got a few quick questions
然后你就可以做自己的事了  哥们
and then you can do your thing, dawg.
你这周和马克说过话吗
Did you talk to Mark at all this week?
关于他的车  孩子
About his bike. And his kid.
在你看来他有什么不正常的吗
Okay, did he seem off to you at all?
他的行为有什么不同吗
Was his behavior different in any way?
他看起来像是要去炸几栋楼的样子吗
Did he seem like he was gonna blow up a couple of buildings?
并没有
No, he didn't.
马克很易怒  但是他并不是个冷酷无情的人
Mark gets hot, but he's not hard.
他甚至都没有和那个播新闻的女的说过话
He never even talked to that news lady.
如果有什么的话  也是他在保护她
If anything, he protected her.
他想保护雪莉  你看到了吗
He tried to protect Sheri, you saw this?
有人进来和雪莉说话
Look, some guy came in to talked to Sheri.
他很反常  大叫着什么
He was all jacked up and screaming about something
她写的新闻博客  八卦博客还是什么的
she wrote or some news blog or gossip blog or something,
马克强迫他离开了大楼
and Mark forced him from the building.
这是什么时候的事  他长什么样
Okay, when was this and what did he look like?
白人  和我差不多大
It was a white guy, about my age.
我记得他有胡子
I think he had a beard.
-好  -谢谢
- Okay. - Thank you.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
舒曼要去趟洗手间
Giving Shuman a bathroom break?
怎么我每次一给舒曼分配任务
How is it every time I give Shuman desk assignment
他就要上厕所  你好  华莱士
his bladder fails him? Hey, Wallace.
如果要选择一天休息的话
You know, if there was ever a day to take off
一定是在有人想要炸飞你后的那天
it would be the day after someone tried to blow you up.
你可以休息一天的  整理整理你的头发
You could take a day, you know. Get your hair done.
-我的头发怎么了  -没什么
- What's wrong with my hair? - Not a thing.
没什么  就是人们会做的事
Not a thing. Just something people do.
又一个因为假新闻被炸的无辜的人
芝加哥警署还有做假新闻的犯罪者
都会被炸成灰烬
就像我祖母  她在她做了头发之后休息了一天
Like my grandmother, she takes a day and get her hair done.
-并不是说我...  -伯吉斯  伯吉斯
- Not that I am in anyway... - Burgess, Burgess.
-说我祖...  -伯吉斯
- Referring to you as my grand-- - Burgess!
所有人
Everyone!
不要用无线电  不要碰你的手机
Don't key your radios. Don't touch your phones.
伯吉斯  我要你下楼
Burgess, I want you to go downstairs
把囚犯都铐起来  带他们出去
shackle up the prisoners and lead them outside.
我疏散楼上
I'll evacuate upstairs.
我们现在得疏散这个区域
We need to clear the district now.
炸弹已经拆除了
Device has been defused.
我们正在搜查  看看还有没有别的装置
We're doing a sweep for any secondary devices.
我们会尽快让你们进去的
We'll get you in as soon as we can.
知道是什么了吗
Do we know what it was?
某种廉价  粗糙的简易爆炸装置
Uh, some cheap, crude IED.
我觉得那玩意不会爆炸的
I don't think the thing would have gone off.
和我们的罪犯不符
That doesn't fit with our offender.
有符合的地方也有不符合的地方
It does and it doesn't.
同样的材料  同样的标记
Same material. Same signature.
我们会调查成分
We'll investigate the components,
但是就是他
but this is him.
只是很快做了这个
Just built this one fast.
会尽快让你们进去的
Get you in as soon as we can.
很快做好
Built it fast.
我们把他惹急了
We pissed him off.
他给我们留下了线索  别浪费了
He gave us a lead. Let's not waste it.
那炸弹肯定能查到出处
That device came from somewhere.
等我一下  好  快递方没有线索
Give me a second. All right, we're at a zero with delivery.
炸弹是通过私人下单
The device was delivered and mailed
用优比速快递交付和运送的
from a UPS store by a private shipper.
单子是网上下单的
The order for pickup was made online
用的是预付货币卡  好  继续说吧
with a prepaid money card. Yeah, I'm back.
顾客要求到
Customer requested the box be picked up
谢尔单的一处住宅取件
at a residential address on Sheirdan.
-房子是空的  -查一下房契
- House is vacant. - Check the deeds.
查一下过去二十年经手的每一个业主
Run every single property owner in the past two decades.
-好  -给盒子和炸弹匆匆验了一下DNA
- Yeah. - Box and device are being rushed through for DNA,
但被用漂白剂抹掉了
but it was wiped with bleach.
拆弹小组说和另两个炸弹
Bomb squad said same materials
用的是一样的材料
as our other two devices.
很普通  在商店就能买到
It's generic, store bought.
我们走到死胡同里了
We'd be running down dead-ends.
继续查
Well, run them anyway.
在我们宣告之前没有什么死胡同
We don't assume anything is dead until we pronounce it.
我拿到装箱单上便条的副本了
I got copies of the note that was on the packing slip.
"又一个因为假新闻
"Once again an innocent man blown up
被炸的无辜的人
by the engine of fake news.
芝加哥警署  还有做假新闻的
The CPD, further perpetrators
犯罪者都会被炸成灰烬"
of the fake news engine will burn."
他说的是马克
He's talking about Mark.
那个保安
The security guard?
马克是无辜的
Mark's got to be the innocent man.
"又一次"  "又一次"
"Once again." "Once again." I mean...
他这么说假新闻
He's referring to fake news
好像跟他亲近的人被它害过
as if it's blown up someone close to him before.
-这是私怨  -找到了
- It's personal. - Found it.
马克的朋友提到的八卦博客
The gossip blog Mark's friend mentioned.
雪莉没有正式去工作过
Sheri never officially worked for one.
但有一个博客  "芝加哥独家新闻"
But there was a blog. "The Chicago Scoop."
两年前雪莉在西北部时它很活跃
It was active Sheri's last two years at Northwestern.
这个网站报导八卦  丑闻
The site reported on gossip, scandal,
任何值得一扒的事情
anything that was pull-the-rug worthy.
所有的东西都是匿名的  但历史记录
Whole thing was anonymous, but the historical data,
IP地址  是雪莉  她在运营
IPs, it was Sheri. She ran it.
雪莉在上面写了一个毁人生活的故事
Sheri wrote a story there that tore someone's life apart.
埃里克也报导了同一个故事
And Eric reported on that same story.
那就对了
I mean, that would fit.
好  我们查查看
All right, let's run with it.
所以我们不用把马克关48小时  对吗
So we're not gonna hold Mark on the whole 48, right?
炸弹送来时他已经被拘留了
He was in custody when the bomb was sent.
不符合侧写
Doesn't fit the profile,
而且他家里有妻有女
and he's got a wife and a daughter at home.
是的  我知道  但不管有没有新的侧写
Yeah, I know, but new profile or not
我们都还没完全洗清他的嫌疑  所以
we haven't cleared him fully yet, so...
什么
What?
他的人生就要被网络给毁了
His life's getting destroyed online.
是的
Yeah.
再多一天也是一样  所以
I mean, one more day won't change that, so.
蛋糕  墨西哥卷
-你气色不错  -并没有
- You look good. - No, I don't.
丽贝卡离开我了
Rebecca left me.
现在我天天吃必胜客
Now all I do is eat Pizza Hut
看美剧重播
and watch reruns of "M.A.S.H."
这个不是我给你的
This didn't come from me.
我们组在查一个跟这个贩子有关的案子
Guys in my unit are running a case on this dealer,
所以我想低调一点
so I wanna play it close to the vest.
阿里·贝龙  他很厉害吗
Ali Beron. He big time?
还行吧
Decent.
大部分时间在买卖火炮
Mostly deals in artillery,
但一年前他在卖C4
but he was selling C-4 a year ago.
是你们要找的东西
It was your stuff.
我们本来想抓他  但他听到了风声
Now, we were gonna make him, but he got tipped.
我们到他在中西部的老窝时那里已经空了
By the time we got to his Midwest hub, place was empty.
知道炸弹在哪儿吧
We know where the C-4's at, huh?
如果有消息  早就给你了
If we had a tip, we would have given it to you.
但我们离高手阿里越来越近了
But we're getting close to the nailing Ali
因为印第安纳波利斯的一个小道消息
because this small time fence in Indianapolis
说他在他那买了三个火箭推进榴弹  很便宜
says he bought three RPGs from him a year ago, cheap.
说他那还卖别的
Said there's more to buy,
但他只对重型武器感兴趣
but he was only interested in the heavy stuff.
所以我要找一个小道消息源
So I'm looking for a small-time fence.
说实话  卖C4那家伙
Honestly, the guy selling the C-4s
可能是从他仓库里拿来的
probably some dude hocking it from his garage.
阿里想要甩货
Ali just wanted to dump his product.
肯定会在社会底层见缝插针
Gonna be a needle in a lot of low-life hay.
我就在社会底层
Well, low-life hay's where I live.
所以我们认为埃里克和雪莉成为目标
So we think that Eric and Sheri were targeted
是因为他们都报导了
for a story that they both reported on
煽动性新闻
something inflammatory.
雪莉在博客里写那三百多篇文章时
Being as Sheri wrote over 300 articles for her blog
埃里克正在"电讯报"上班  所以
while Eric worked here at the Telegraph, so...
我们想着也许你会想起来这里面
We were hoping that one of these would jump out at you
有也埃里克写过的故事
as a story that Eric would have worked on too.
对不起  雪莉的文章大部分都是
I'm sorry, most of Sheri's articles
流行文化和八卦
are pop culture and gossip.
埃里克在这时做的是特约记者
When Eric worked here he was a stringer.
-他跟踪报导犯罪故事吗  -凶杀案
- He chased crime stories? - Homicides.
恩格尔伍德  加菲公园  血案枪战
Englewood, Garfield Park, daily blood and bullets.
必须得是严重到能毁掉
It would have to be something with enough weight
一个人的生活的事
to disrupt someone's life.
埃里克不是写过拉里·谢帕德的故事吗
Didn't Eric run the Larry Shepard story?
-什么故事  -谢帕德
- What story was that? - Shepard.
他以前是这里的记者  调查记者
He was a reporter here, investigative journalist.
是个好人  大概两年前被解雇了
Was a good guy, fired about two years ago.
他为什么被解雇
Why was he fired?
谢帕德一直在报导一件谋杀案
Shepard had been reporting on a murder
然后其它地方开始谣言四起
and then rumors started circulating at other outlets
说其实是他...
that he was in some way...
谋杀了那个人
that he had murdered the woman.
一个记者被指控犯下了他正在报导的案子
A journalist being accused of the very crime he was reporting?
-你可以想象  -这事被报导了吗
- You can imagine. - That got press time?
很多
Lots of it.
我们报社没做错
Look, our paper did the right thing.
那简直是公关噩梦  他们只能解雇谢帕德
It was a PR nightmare. They had to fire Shepard.
好的  所以谢帕德因为谋杀被捕了吗
Okay, so Shepard got arrested for the murder?
不是  天啊  不是
No. God, no.
根本是无稽之谈
It was nonsense.
所以你们因为一个假新闻
So you guys blew up your reporter's career
毁了自家记者的事业
based on fake news.
是的  他永远不会原谅我们
Yeah, he never forgave us for that.
他自己的报社  自己的专栏
His own paper, his own column.
我几周前在地铁看到他
I saw him a couple of weeks ago on the L.
他一看到我就大喊大叫
Started yelling when he saw me.
拉里·谢帕德  四十几岁有胡须的白人男性
Larry Shepard. White male, 40s, beard.
符合特征
It matches.
关灯
Go dark.
收集粒子
没有发现危险
停
Hold.
走
Go.
警长  谢帕德名下的每辆车都发出通缉了
Hey, Sarge, put a BOLO out on every car Shepard's ever owned.
他住过的小区都去走访过了
Canvassing every neighborhood he's ever lived in.
中心区在约谈亲朋
Area Central's talking to friends and family,
但是老大  我得说  这个人
but, boss, I got to tell you this guy,
他准备得很充分
he was prepared for this.
过去三个月他没有用过自己的手机
He hasn't used his cell phone in over three months.
一张信用卡都没  交管局什么都没查到
Not a single credit card. CTA hit nothing.
他清空了他的社交网站  银行账户  邮箱
He wiped his social media, bank accounts, email.
这家伙就活在暗处
This guy's living in the dark.
我不知道我们要怎么才能找到他
I don't know how we're gonna find him.
-警长  -嗯
- Sergeant. - Yeah.
道森和厄普顿一直待在谢帕德家里  没动静
Dawson and Upton are sitting on Shepard's house, no movement.
是吧  我怀疑以后也没有  好的
Yeah, I doubt there will be. All right.
把我们知道的告诉我
Just walk me through what we know.
-好吗  -好的
- Okay? - Okay.
两年前谢帕德在调查鸦林镇
Two years ago Shepard was investigating the brutal murder
一位年轻女性被残忍杀害的案子
of this young woman in Ravenswood.
-好的  -雪莉
- Okay. - Sheri,
在经营自己的博客时发现了
while working her blog, noticed,
你应该会说  强制扭曲了他的故事
I guess you would call it, an obsessive bent to his story
因为雪莉在好几篇文章里提到了她漂亮有魅力
because in multiple articles Shepard refers to her beauty, radiance.
雪莉觉得奇怪
Sheri thought it was off.
所以就深挖了一下
So she dug into it.
她发现谢帕德
She found out Shepard
认识被杀的女性
knew the woman who was murdered.
她就在推特里写了一条信息
She wrote a tweet in her blog.
开玩笑说是谢帕德犯的案
A joke accusing Shepard of the crime.
"我调查并破了鸦林镇的谋杀案
"I went ahead and solved the Ravenswood murder.
线索如下  谢帕德当晚在哪里"
Here's a clue: Where was Shepard the night of?"
所以她就因为一个两句话的玩笑被杀了吗
So she was murdered over this two-sentence joke?
是的  她从没写过其它关于谢帕德的东西
Yeah, she never wrote anything else on Shepard.
也没见过他
Never even met him.
她就因为这几个字被杀了
She was killed over those 140 characters.
这条推特被传播出去  大肆报道
The tweet gets spread, picked up, reported,
然后谢帕德就被解雇了
and then Shepard, he gets fired.
我们的人调查过他
Our people investigated him.
他们发现没一个字是真的
They found almost none of it was true.
我看了凶杀报告
I read the homicide report.
他们几乎马上洗脱了他的嫌疑
They basically cleared him from the jump.
两个月后他们找到了真正的凶手
They found the real killer a couple months later.
是的  没用了
Yeah, didn't matter though.
谢帕德找不到别的工作
Shepard couldn't get another job.
他的妻子离开了他  然后三个月前
His wife left him, then three months ago
她自杀了
she commits suicide.
我想他应该是崩溃了
I guess he just broke.
他想要清除自己的电子痕迹
He did try to erase his digital footprint,
但信息调查部从一个被删的账户找到了这个
but CPIK was able to pull this from a deleted account.
人总会付出代价
There comes a time when people pay,
为自己的行为
when their actions matter,
为自己在虚拟世界诽谤别人时
when the libel they spit into the ether
所吐出的口水  这些账都会清算
of a virtual landscape has a reckoning.
新闻行业必须要负起责任
Journalism needs to be accountable.
人必须得有责任心
People need to be responsible.
所以他这样已经有一段时间了
All right, so he goes on like that for quite a while.
我们知道他接下来会袭击哪里吗
Do we know where he's gonna be hitting next?
如果我们假设他会把
If we assume that he's gonna target
报导过他的记者作为下一个目标
a journalist that reported on him,
那可能的人是这六个
then we got these half a dozen possities.
现在  我们想把这些人聚集起来
Now, we're trying to round these people up, but--
谢帕德可能已经布置好了炸弹
Shepard could have bombs planted already.
-是的  -所以我们大概落后这家伙七步
- Right. - So we're like seven steps behind this guy.
好  现在这是第一要案
All right, let's make it a priority.
把所有可能是目标的人都带回来
Bring in anyone who might be a target.
我有个人可能知道谢帕德在哪里
All right, I got a guy who might know where Shepard
买的C4  我让人带他来了
bought his C-4. I had Tact bring him in.
-需要个人跟我一起  -好
- Could use a second. - Yeah.
-都打开  -好
- Put the rest of that thing on. - You got it.
不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
我不用再跟你说话了
I don't have to talk to you anymore.
我已经跟那个案子没关系了
I worked that case off.
-我只是有几个问题  -不不  我现在变好了
- I just got a couple of questions- - No, no! I'm better now.
听着  重点是  我所有的线人
Listen, the thing is, all my CIs,
都让我找你  马尔科姆
they pointed me to you, Malcolm.
他们说你还忙着
They say that you're still busy.
不是了  我变好了
No, I ain't. I'm better.
不  他们说你还在做你的小玩意儿
No, they say you're still making your little gadgets.
我就只需要
So now all I need is
贩卖C4的一个小贩子的名字
the name of a small time fence dealing C-4.
不  我不造武器了  我变好了
No, I don't make weapons no more. I'm better.
那是手机吗
Is that a cell phone?
不能让那个靠近我  好吗  不行
You can't bring that near me, okay? You can't.
我不能接触手机  否则就完了
I can't be around those things. This is how it's gonna end.
-否则就完了  -好  好
- This is how it's all gonna end. - Okay, okay,
我收起来
I'll put it away.
-他告诉你什么了吗  -没有
- He give you anything? - No.
拜托  我们就只要一个名字  马尔科姆
Come on. All we need is a name, Malcolm.
我说过了  我现在变好了
No, I told you. I'm better now.
我猜你别无选择
You don't have a choice I guess.
他会去搜查你的住处  马尔科姆
He's gonna--he's gonna search your place, Malcolm.
如果让他找到任何违反你假释规定的东西
Now, if he finds anything that violates your parole,
化学品  武器等等
chemicals, weapons, whatever,
他都会拿走
he's gonna take it.
或者你可以告诉我们一个名字
Or you can just give us a name
然后你跟没见过我们一样回你的家
and you get to go home like you never saw us.
-好  -什么样的
- All right. - What kind?
块状军用炸药
Military grade in bricks.
2012年制造
Manufactured in 2012.
那个小贩子可能
Small time fence would have probably
今年才开始卖
just started selling it this year.
乔治·李尔
George Lehr.
乔治·李尔  我们见过这个混蛋
George Lehr. We met this prick.
他是埃里克·米切尔爆炸案的目击者
He was a witness at Eric Mitchel's explosion.
他主动提出帮我们
He offered to help us.
我们让他在现场填了目击者报告
We had him fill out a witness report on the scene,
还让他留了驾照信息
made him give a driver's license.
我和亚当顺道查了他的身份证
Adam and I checked out his ID by the way.
-是合法的  -但他是卖谢帕德用的C4的贩子
- It's legit. - But he's our fence. Sold the C-4 Shepard's using.
也就是说他们有联系
Which means they were in contact.
何以见得
Okay, we know this how?
李尔脸书时间线上的信息
Messages on Lehr's Facebook timeline.
两个月有五条  每条都是用
Five in two months, each one posted
不同的小号发的
from a different dummy profile.
三天前另一个小号
Then three days ago another dummy profile
只发了一个邮箱地址
posted nothing but an email address.
那个邮箱地址已经关了
The email address has since been shut down,
但我觉得是谢帕德的
but I think it was Shepard.
好  要去抓他吗
All right. So you want to take him?
不
No.
我们好不容易查到了谢帕德的线索
I mean, we finally got a lead to Shepard.
我不想搞砸
I don't want to blow it.
暗中搜查李尔的房子
Look, get coverts on Lehr's house.
尽可能找到关于这家伙的信息
Find out everything about this guy.
如果他们两个有联系  那我们得想办法
If these two are on contact, we got to figure out
在李尔不知道的情况下先下手
a way to get ahead of it without Lehr knowing.
你应该去释放马克了
Hey, you should probably go ahead and release Mark.
我说得很清楚了
I made myself real damn clear
没有律师坐在我旁边
I'm not talking to anyone without my lawyer
我不会跟任何人说话
sitting next to me.
我不是来审你的
Not here to interrogate you.
你可以走了
You're free to go.
不起诉吗
So no charge?
不起诉  先生
No, sir.
你甚至没勇气跟我道歉
You don't even have the stomach to apologize.
你可以走了
You're free to go.
迪亚哥来电
什么事
Yeah, what's up?
什么
What?
她在打包是什么意思  我马上来
What do you mean she's packing? I'm on my way.
你有什么计划
All right, so what's the plan then?
我不想一个人被软禁在你的公寓里
Well, I don't really want to spend the weekend alone
度过这个周末
on house arrest in your apartment.
-好  -我本来打算去妈妈那里
- Yeah. - And I was gonna go to Mom's,
但她今晚在男朋友家过夜
but she's sleeping over at a boyfriend's.
你就这么急着离开吗
So just hightail it out of here, huh?
我要去玛拉阿姨那里
I'm going to Aunt Mara's.
慢着  慢着
Wait, wait.
去底特律
In Detroit?
你要大半夜一个人
You're gonna take a bus alone
-坐汽车吗  -是的
- in the middle of the night? - Yes.
爸爸  我要去一个
Yeah, Dad, I'm gonna somewhere
能受得了现在的我的地方
where people can stand who I've become.
伊娃  我不是说...
Eva, you know I didn't mean--
不  你知道什么最让我伤心吗
No, you know what hurts most?
是你根本不给我解释的机会
You didn't give me a chance to explain, okay?
我去那个派对是接我喝醉的朋友
I went to that party to pick up my drunk friend.
她不能开车
So she wouldn't drive.
然后他们把那些照片发到了网上
Then they all posted these pictures online
突然就看起来像我在那里开派对了
and suddenly it looks like I was there partying.
但其实我没有
But I wasn't.
你不能凭一张照片决定我是谁
You can't decide who I am off of a picture.
也不能凭人对照片的反应决定
Or how people react to a picture.
你说得对
You're right.
我应该让你解释
I should have let you explain.
是我弄错了
I got that wrong.
对不起
I'm sorry.
谢谢
Thank you.
我还是删除了你的第二个账号
I still deleted your second account though.
因为那样很危险  伊娃
Because that stuff is dangerous, Eva.
听我说
No, look, listen.
你得至少让我保护你
You have to at least let me try to protect you.
我只是想保护你
That's what I want to do. That's it.
我还得去跟一个人道歉
I have another apology I have to make.
温斯洛  怎么了
Winslow, what happened?
有人扔砖头砸玻璃
Couple of bricks through the window.
一个12岁的孩子被碎玻璃砸到了
Shattered glass at a 12-year-old.
她不会有事  只是吓得不轻
She'll be fine. She's just scared out of her mind.
-知道是谁扔的吗  -不知道
- Do you know who threw them? - No.
那家人说他们也不知道
Family says they have no idea.
是跟爆炸案有关的
It's linked to the bombings.
是那个网民认出的人家
It's the guy the internet ID'd.
他们家里接到了很多电话
They've been getting a lot of calls addressed to the house.
他太倒霉了
Guy's one unlucky dude.
下次你们可能就在附近了
Maybe you guys'll be around next time.
好  非常感谢你的时间
Okay, thank you very much for your time.
晚安
Nightly, you know.
-帮帮忙  -好的
- Help me out. - All right.
芝加哥消防局
-警长  -嗯
- Sarge. - Yeah.
我想到办法对付李尔了
I think I have a way in with Lehr.
虽然不正规  但这样能到他家里
It's a bit unorthodox, but we would get his house,
拿到他的邮件  而他不会知道
his emails. He wouldn't know a thing.
告诉安东尼奥  我要他跟我一起去
Tell Antonio. I want him there with me.
好
Okay.
有很多潜在的目标
It's a potential of dozens of targets.
虽然我们在尽快把他们
I mean we're working to get those mentioned
纳入保护性监禁
prominently into protective custody,
但需要时间
but it takes time.
而且我们是在预测  队长
And we're making predictions here, Chief.
我们无法确定接下来他的目标是谁
We can't be confident we know where he's going next.
好  我们会尽力帮忙
All right. We'll help you any way we can.
-谢谢  -救援队下班了
- Thank you. - Squad's off shift.
西弗莱德肯定会乐意帮忙
Severide would be happy to jump on transport.
很感谢  但我们需要的不是他们
I appreciate that, but it's not what we need.
我们需要你们的急救员
We need your paramedics.
我们有理由相信谢帕德
We strongly believe Shepard's
跟一个叫乔治·李尔的有联系
in contact with a man, George Lehr.
而李尔是个贩子
Now, Lehr's a fence.
我们相信他们二人
We believe the pair's actively
-是通过邮件联系的  -李尔
- keeping in touch through email. - Lehr?
-我认识他吗  -是的
- Do I know that name? - Yeah, you do.
你和我妹妹在过去半年
You and my sister responded to his house
去他家出警过三次
three times in the last six months.
-他心脏有问题  -不行
- He has a heart condition. - No.
队长  我们需要在李尔不知道的情况下
Chief, look, we need real-time access
实时接入他的邮件  笔记本电脑
to Lehr's emails, his laptop, without him knowing.
我说了  不行
I said no.
队长  我们可以的
Chief, we can do this.
听着
Look.
绝对不能危及到我的急救员
You will not endanger my paramedics.
我们需要进入李尔的房子  复制他的笔记本
We need to get inside Lehr's house to clone his laptop.
我需要你们帮我们进去
I need you to get us in the door.